<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>No Lag Mind</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on No Lag Mind</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.151.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Vision for the Best Note Taking App</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/sixth_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/sixth_post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;details &gt;
  &lt;summary markdown=&#34;span&#34;&gt;Blog Summary - Click to expand&lt;/summary&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;A critique of existing note apps and a vision for a better tool. Key points:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Problem&lt;/strong&gt;: Current apps like Obsidian and Anytype lack dynamic flexibility or keyboard-centric design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Vision&lt;/strong&gt;: A fast, keyboard-controlled app where everything is a node.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Features&lt;/strong&gt;: Support for mind maps, kanban, and complex checklists within a markdown environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Goal&lt;/strong&gt;: A fluid, local-first tool that adapts to your thought process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Keyboard Shortcuts: How to Work at the Speed of Thought</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/fifth_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/fifth_post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;details &gt;
  &lt;summary markdown=&#34;span&#34;&gt;Blog Summary - Click to expand&lt;/summary&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;How to work at the &amp;lsquo;speed of thought&amp;rsquo; using keyboard shortcuts. Key strategies:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Touch Typing&lt;/strong&gt;: Improving WPM reduces cognitive load and reliance on the mouse.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Workflow Efficiency&lt;/strong&gt;: Minimize errors and posture issues to maintain flow.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Essential Shortcuts&lt;/strong&gt;: A curated list of system, file management, and text editing shortcuts for Mac.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hidden Gems&lt;/strong&gt;: Advanced shortcuts for screenshots, window management, and system control.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;why-typing-speed-matters-everywhere&#34;&gt;Why typing speed matters everywhere&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I mentioned the idea of working at the speed of thought, where you can think of what you need to do and it can just happen, almost like your laptop is controlled by your mind. Besides all the apps that you can use and all the settings that you can configure to help you accomplish this work style, the one thing that connects all of the tools is that you use is, your keyboard. This means that the more fluent with your keyboard you are and the faster that you can type, the more things and the quicker you can get things done.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Flat to Fast: The Science of Full‑Travel Keyboards Top Typists Rely On</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/fourth_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/fourth_post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;details &gt;
  &lt;summary markdown=&#34;span&#34;&gt;Blog Summary - Click to expand&lt;/summary&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Why top typists prefer full-travel mechanical keyboards over low-profile ones. Key insights:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Switches&lt;/strong&gt;: Clicky/tactile switches provide feedback that improves speed and accuracy compared to linear switches.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keycaps&lt;/strong&gt;: Sculpted profiles (OEM/Cherry) help fingers locate keys without looking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Layout&lt;/strong&gt;: Standard QWERTY and staggered layouts benefit from years of muscle memory.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Low Profile Drawbacks&lt;/strong&gt;: Less feedback, reduced travel distance, and flatter keycaps can hinder rhythm and accuracy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Perfect AI Prompt Formula: How to Get Exactly What You Want Every Time</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/third_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/third_post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;details &gt;
  &lt;summary markdown=&#34;span&#34;&gt;Blog Summary - Click to expand&lt;/summary&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Learn a five-part formula to get the best results from AI models. Key points:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Persona&lt;/strong&gt;: Assign a role (e.g., &amp;rsquo;expert coder&amp;rsquo;) to guide the AI&amp;rsquo;s perspective.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Context&lt;/strong&gt;: Provide relevant background to tailor the response.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Task&lt;/strong&gt;: Clearly state what you want the AI to do.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Output Style&lt;/strong&gt;: Define the desired format and tone.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Negatives&lt;/strong&gt;: Specify what to avoid to filter out unwanted content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;why-you-should-take-the-time-to-learn-to-prompt&#34;&gt;Why you should take the time to learn to prompt&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When most people are writing a prompt to an LLM they only write a sentence or two. While this is straight forward, it normally leads to generic results that sometimes aren&amp;rsquo;t even helpful.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The No-Click Principle: Why Your Mouse is Slowing You Down (and How to Fix It)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/seccond_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/seccond_post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;details &gt;
  &lt;summary markdown=&#34;span&#34;&gt;Blog Summary - Click to expand&lt;/summary&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This post introduces the &amp;lsquo;No-Click Principle&amp;rsquo; to boost productivity by minimizing mouse usage. Key takeaways:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Cost of Clicking&lt;/strong&gt;: Reaching for the mouse breaks flow and wastes time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speed of Thought&lt;/strong&gt;: Aim to navigate your device as fast as you think using keyboard-only workflows.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tools&lt;/strong&gt;: Apps like Raycast, Homerow, and Vimium enable mouse-free navigation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vim Keybindings&lt;/strong&gt;: Learning Vim keys is a high-leverage skill for efficient text and system navigation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to My Blog</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/first_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/first_post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;details &gt;
  &lt;summary markdown=&#34;span&#34;&gt;Blog Summary - Click to expand&lt;/summary&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This blog explores productivity, programming, and learning systems. Key topics include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Programming &amp;amp; Game Dev&lt;/strong&gt;: Insights into building tools, games, and automation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keyboard Mastery&lt;/strong&gt;: Comparisons, ergonomics, and typing philosophy for speed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learning Systems&lt;/strong&gt;: Techniques to master new skills efficiently.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI Workflows&lt;/strong&gt;: How to prompt effectively and use AI as a powerful assistant.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome! This is my first post - and a promise. I&amp;rsquo;ll be publishing here every day with small, useful snippets of knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi there! I&amp;rsquo;m a 14-year-old who absolutely loves making things and playing with words. Whether I&amp;rsquo;m coding up a new project, crafting a story, or building something cool with my hands, I&amp;rsquo;m always excited to create and share what I&amp;rsquo;ve learned along the way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I believe that the best way to learn is by doing, and the best way to grow is by sharing. That&amp;rsquo;s why I started this blog - to document my journey of discovery and hopefully inspire others to start their own creative adventures.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural Language Calculator</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/natural-language-calculator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/natural-language-calculator/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This calculator lets you type math at the same speed you type words. No more hunting for numbers and special characters—just use your normal typing speed and the letter keyboard to perform calculations. The experience is simple, fluid, and lag-free, making math feel as natural as writing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you prefer spelling out numbers (like &amp;ldquo;one seven two&amp;rdquo;) or using traditional digits, this calculator understands both. You can mix and match numbers and words however feels most natural to you, giving you the flexibility to work the way you want.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/project/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Explore my collection of projects and tools.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
