<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>No Lag Mind</title>
    <link>http://localhost:52887/</link>
    <description>Recent content on No Lag Mind</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.151.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:52887/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>From Flat to Fast: The Science of Full‑Travel Keyboards Top Typists Rely On</title>
      <link>http://localhost:52887/posts/fourth_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:52887/posts/fourth_post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-keyboards-can-allow-you-to-type-at-300-wpm&#34;&gt;What keyboards can allow you to type at 300 wpm?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Besides the insane amount of skill and practice that it takes to be able to type that fast, which keyboard you have could effect how fast you can type a lot. This is why all the top typists carefully pick, mod, and use every keyboard that they get.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every mechanical keyboard has three main comments that effect the typing experience: switches, keycaps, and layout.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Perfect AI Prompt Formula: How to Get Exactly What You Want Every Time</title>
      <link>http://localhost:52887/posts/third_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:52887/posts/third_post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;why-you-should-take-the-time-to-learn-to-prompt&#34;&gt;Why you should take the time to learn to prompt&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When most people are writing a prompt to an LLM they only write a sentence or two. While this is straight forward, it normally leads to generic results that sometimes aren&amp;rsquo;t even helpful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The solution to this is to take the time to write a nice prompt that is catered to your certain use case. When writing a good prompt there is a specific structure to follow, which both makes it easer to start writing the prompt and for the LLM to understand what you want. By following the five-part formula you can ensure that you will always get a response from the AI that is useful for your specific use case.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The No-Click Principle: Why Your Mouse is Slowing You Down (and How to Fix It)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:52887/posts/seccond_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:52887/posts/seccond_post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-is-the-no-click-principle&#34;&gt;What is the no-click principle?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is the idea that taking your hand of the keyboard to reach for the mouse will significantly reduce your productivity. This is because of the time and context switch costs:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Time Cost:&lt;/strong&gt; Every reach for the mouse is a few seconds lost.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Context Switch Cost:&lt;/strong&gt; More critically, you interrupt your &lt;strong&gt;flow state&lt;/strong&gt;. You have to visually locate and track the cursor, and when you return to the keyboard, you have to mentally and physically reset your typing position.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even though it might only take a couple seconds to do all the above and then get back to typing, if you add up those few seconds for all the times it happens in a day, week, or month, it can start to become hours of time that you could have otherwise spent working or thinking.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to My Blog</title>
      <link>http://localhost:52887/posts/first_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:52887/posts/first_post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome! This is my first post - and a promise. I&amp;rsquo;ll be publishing here every day with small, useful snippets of knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What you’ll find:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pillars: programming, game dev, keyboards/typing, learning systems, and AI.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;programming&#34;&gt;Programming&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like to build things, from small tools and automation scripts to entire games or course websites. I plan to share the process and ideas that go into making these tools here with you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;game-development&#34;&gt;Game development&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m currently building two indie games and have always found interest in coding something that I can actually play. So I would like to share that passion with you, weather it is a small update or reworking all the art.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:52887/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:52887/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi there! I&amp;rsquo;m a 14-year-old who absolutely loves making things and playing with words. Whether I&amp;rsquo;m coding up a new project, crafting a story, or building something cool with my hands, I&amp;rsquo;m always excited to create and share what I&amp;rsquo;ve learned along the way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I believe that the best way to learn is by doing, and the best way to grow is by sharing. That&amp;rsquo;s why I started this blog - to document my journey of discovery and hopefully inspire others to start their own creative adventures.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
